#### Contact

7314415699 (Mobile) mtgelliott15@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/andrewelliott-501008163 (LinkedIn) critchkn.github.io (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

Web Development **JavaScript** Responsive Web Design

### Certifications

Responsive Web Design Certification

# **Andrew Elliott**

Web Content Specialist at The Creative Group

Greater Nashville Area, TN

## Summary

I'm a Front-end Developer in the Greater Nashville Area with a focus on Front-end languages and Frameworks such as Javascript, Vue.js and Node.js.

I specialize in Americans with Disabilities (ADA) Compliance, following WCAG 2.0 compliance standards.

I have a very unique set of skills, skills that I've acquired over my career, that allow me to help companies like yours.

## Experience

Scrybe Digital Web Developer January 2019 - Present **United States** 

Helping customers drive profits by ensuring their web based branding is above reproach by utilizing Content Management Systems such as Wordpress and Wix, as well as Front-End Development Languages, Libraries and Frameworks like Javascript, Vue.js, Node.js and Bootstrap 3/4.

The Creative Group Web Content Specialist July 2018 - Present

Nashville, Tennessee

Contracted as an ADA Specialist, I am tasked with bringing HCA branded websites into WCAG 2.0 Compliance while using technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Libraries such as Bootstrap 4 and the Content Management System, dotCMS.

Digital Dream Forge QA Software Quality Assurance Analyst January 2018 - April 2018 (4 months)

Cookeville, TN

Utilizing an SQL database, I helped to ensure rewardStyle hyperlinks were linking correctly to their influencers website.

As well, I performed other QA tasks, ensuring the application Marvel Contest of Champions was bug free and ready for deployment.

New Life

Winchester, Tn

Direct Support Professional August 2013 - December 2015 (2 years 5 months)

In a house and day center setting, I helped mentally handicapped individuals conquer their day to day challenges, specifically working with individuals on the Autistic Spectrum.

Ranging from helping sweep floors and keeping their rooms clean, to helping out at their place of employment, I ensured their day to day lives were as seamless as anyone's.

## Education

freeCodeCamp

Frontend Development · (2018 - 2019)

Bethel University

None, History · (2011 - 2013)